Mss.B.Ey83
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 12, 1853; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 15, 1853; 10x8; Liverpool (England). Public Libraries, Museums, and Art Gallery
    Liverpool, Printed L.filled in in ms.S.: Sam[ue]l Holme. 1p.and add. Thanks for species.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, London, Nov. 17, 1853; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Dunker, Wilhelm, 1809-1885
    Cassel, A.L.S. 2p.and add. Concerning shells. Refers to Pfeiffer.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 17, 1853; 11x8; Moricand, Stefano, 1780-1854
    Geneva, A.L.S. 2p. In French. Concerning plants. Friendly letter, referring to Boissier, Hooker, Reeve.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 18, 1853; 7x4-1/2; Egerton, Philip de Malpas, Sir, 1806-1881
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning shells. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, London, Dec. 31, 1853; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Bridges, Thomas, 1807-1865
    Valparaiso, A.L.S. 3p.and add. Concerning seeds, botany, shells, and insects.
  - Concerning the death of H. E. Strickland, [1853]; Newspaper clipping.
  - Letter to T[homas C.] Eyton, Jan. 19, 1854; 7x4-1/2; Cuming, Hugh, 1791-1865
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning shells and birds.
  - Hitcham Horticultural Show…, Program, July 12, 1854; Printed.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, London, Oct. 14, 1854; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Bridges, Thomas, 1807-1865
    Valparaiso, A.L.S. 1p.and add. Forwards boxes of shells.
  - Concerning the death of Edward Forbes, [Nov 1854]; Newspaper clipping.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Dec. 17, 1854; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Ball, Robert, 1802-1857
    Dublin, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Hugh] Cuming, Jan. 20, 1855; 8-1/2x5; Deshayes, G. P. (Gérard Paul), 1795-1875
    Paris, A.L.S. 4p. In French. Concerning shells. Refers to Bernardi, Edwards and Reeve.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, Feb. 2, 1855; 10-1/2x8; Nappa, R V
    Manila, A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds, plants, and seeds.
  - Letter to [Hugh Cuming], February 14, 1855; 8x5; Macgillivray, John, 1822-1867
    Sydney, A.L.S. 8p. Business. Concerning shells and natural history. Refers to Hooker, Gould and Forbes.
  - Letter to [Hugh] Cuming, March 20, 1855; 8x5-1/2; Pins (?), T
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. In French. Concerning shells and publications. Refers to Bernardi and Pfeiffer.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, London, April 4, 1855; 10x7-1/2; Hohenacker, R F
    Esslinger, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning plants from the Philippines.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 25, 1855; 7x4-1/2; Egerton, Philip de Malpas, Sir, 1806-1881
    A.L.S. 8p. Concerning plants.
  - Letter to [Hugh] Cuming, London, May 7, 1855; 8x6; Recluz, Jean Jacques Elisée, 1830-1905.
    Vaugirard, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In French. Business.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, June 5, 1855; 8x5; Candolle, Alphonse de, 1806-1893
    Geneva, A.L.S. 1p. In French. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, June 10, 1855; 8x5; Fortune, Robert, 1813-1880
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning shells.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, London, June 19, 1855; 10x8; Redfield, John Howard, 1815-1895
    New York, A.L.S. 2p. Thanks for shells and publications. Refers to Pfeiffer, Gould, Gulick and Bland.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Dec. 29, 1855; 7x4-1/2; Gaines, R
    Stoke-upon-Trent, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning shells.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton;], 1855?; 4-1/2x7-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds and shells.
  - Letter to [Thomas Campbell Eyton], March 24, 1856; 9x7; Shuttleworth, R. J. (Robert James), 1810-1874
    Bern, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning shells. Mentions plates missing from volumes he received.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], July 26, 1856; 6-1/2x4; Miles, Charles Popham, 1810-1891
    Arran, A.L.S. 12p. Concerning mollusks. Describes his dredging expedition. Refers to Greville and Balfour.
  - Letter to [Hugh Cuming], Sept. 6, 1856; 7-1/2x5; Boissier, Edouard Pierre, 1810-
    Geneva, A.L.S. 4p. In French. Business.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Sept. 22, 1856; 7x4-1/2; Patterson,, Robert M., (Robert Maskell), 1787-1854
    Belfast, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning oysters. Refers to Emerson Tennent.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 8, 1856; 8x5; Krantz, F., Dr.
    Bonn, A.L.S. 1p. Concerning shells. Business.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 16, 1856; 8x5; Coste, M. (Jean Jacques Marie Cyprien Victor), 1807-1873
    Paris, A.L.S. 1p. In French. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 18, 1856; 5x3-1/2; Miles, Charles Popham, 1810-1891
    Glascow, A.L.S. 4p. Wishes his help in dredging for shells. Invites Eyton to take part in expedition. Refers to Barlee and Greville.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Feb. 5, 1857; 7x4; Forbes, Edward, 1815-1854
    A.L.S. 1p. Asks that books be given to bearer of the letter.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, Feb. 11, 1857; 10x8; Stutchbury, Samuel
    Bristol, A.L.S. 1p. Business.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Feb. 13, 1857; 7x4-1/2; Barlee, Geo.
  - Letter to [Hugh Cuming?], Feb. 18, [1857]; 7x4; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    A.L.S. 1p.,end. Concerning birds. Refers to Eyton.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, Feb 18, 1857; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Sends 3 birds and a paper for Eyton.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, London, March 19, 1857; 9x5-1/2; Klotzsch, Fr. (Friedrich), 1805-1860
    Berlin, A.L.S. 3p. Business.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], March 28, 1857; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning taxes.
  - Letter to [Hugh Cuming], March 29, 1857; 9x5-1/2; Mousson, Albert, 1805-1890
    Zurich, A.L.S. 2p. Orders shells. Refers to Boissier.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 2, 1857; 9x5-1/2; Pfeiffer, Louis Georges Charles, 1805-
    Cassel, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning shells. Refers to Gray and Reeve.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, May 8, 1857; 10-1/2x8; Poey, Felipe, 1799-1891
    Havanna, A.L.S. 1p.and add.: P.P.Carpenter, end. In French. Forwards shells. Refers to Bland.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, July 3, 1857; 8x5; Lea, Isaac, 1792-1886
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning shells. Refers to the Academy of Natural Sciences.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 20, 1857; 9x7-1/2; Fricker, W
    A.L.S. 3p. Lists mollusks.
  - Letter to [Thomas Campbell Eyton], Oct. 19, 1857; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Lenormand, René
    Paris, A.L.S. 1p. In French. Concerning botany. Refers to Hooker.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, Dec 28, 1857; Waits, W. W.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June [8?], 1858; 4-1/2X3-1/2; Henslow, J. S. (John Stevens), 1796-1861
    A.L.S. 4P. Concerning birds. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Jan. 15, 1858; 4-1/2x3-1/2; Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Feb. 15, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Harington, S E
    Exton, A.L.S. 2p. Business. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 12, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning bones and birds. Friendly letter. Refers to George Gray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, England, April 12, 1858; 10-1/2x9; Welsch (?), D
    Colombo, A.L.S. 2p.and add. Concerning pearl oysters.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, April 13, 1858; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Busch, Gerhard van dem, 1791-1868
    Bremen, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning shells. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 14, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    A.L.S. 3p. Wishes to visit him.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, April 19, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Bell, Thomas, 1792-1880
    London, A.L.S. 4p. Hopes he will remain in the Linnean society.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 19, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    Solihull, A.L.S. 3p. Invitation to go hunting.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 19, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Symonds, W. S. (William Samuel), 1818-1887
    Ledbury, A.L.S. 2p. Thanks for arranging his shells. Refers to Jardine.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 20, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Henslow, J. S. (John Stevens), 1796-1861
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. Thanks for items Eyton sent for Village Shows. Sends a paper.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 24, [1858]; 7x4-1/2; Bell, Thomas, 1792-1880
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning the Linnean Society. Concerning mollusks.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, London, May 1, 1858; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Dohrn, H
    Zurich, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning shells. Mentions book he is writing. Friendly letter. Refers to Livesay, Mousson, Pfeiffer, Hanley, and Bielz.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, May 14, 1858; 8-1/2x5; Bland, Thomas, 1809-1885
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning shells. Refers to Swift and Cooper.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 2, 1858; 4-1/2x3-1/2; Patterson,, Robert M., (Robert Maskell), 1787-1854
    A.L.S. 4p. Will send oysters. Refers to Hyndman and Dickie.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 9, 1858; 4-1/2x4; Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning a skeleton.
  - Letter to H[ugh] Cuming, July 10, 1858; 8x5; Newcomb, W
    Glascow, A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter. Refers to Livesay.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 19, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning his work on leeches.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 24, 1858; 7x4; White, Adam, 1817-1879
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds and natural history. Concerning Macgillivray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], July 26, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Hanley, S
    A.L.S. 1p. Concerning mollusks.
  - Letter to [Thomas Campbell Eyton], July 30, 1858; 8x5; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 4p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 31, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    A.L.S. 3p. Wishes to join the Linnean Society.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Aug. 3, 1858; 8x5; Gould, John, 1804-1881
    A.L.S. 2p. Will enter Houghton for a member of the Linnean society. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 4, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Erxleben, J
    London, A.L.S. 1p. Mentions shells. Concerning illustrations prepared by Erxleben.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Aug. 4, 1858; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    A.L.S. 4p. Asks for letter of recommendation.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Aug. 8, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 9, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Erxleben, J
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Cost of printing.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 11, 1858; 8x5; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 11, 1858; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Verreaux, Édouard (Jean Baptiste Édouard), 1810-1868
    Paris, A.L.S. 1p. In French. Concerning skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Aug. 12, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Patterson,, Robert M., (Robert Maskell), 1787-1854
    Belfast, A.L.S. 4p. Business. Refers to Ball.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Aug. 18, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Patterson,, Robert M., (Robert Maskell), 1787-1854
    Belfast, A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 25, 1858; 8x5; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds and skeletons. Refers to Strickland.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 7, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning bird skeletons. Refers to Erxleben.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Sept. 7, 1858; 8x5; Prince, Edwin J.
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter. Refers to Gould.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, Sept. 8, 1858; 10x8; Anthony, John Gould, 1804-1877
    Cincinnati, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning shells. Refers to Binney, T. Say, Bland, and Gray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 15, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 1p. Thanks for birds.
  - Letter to T[homas C.] Eyton, Sept. 16, 1858; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Gray, George Robert, 1808-1872
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 16, 1858; 8x5; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 4p. Friendly letter. Refers to Hobson and Dickinson.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, London, Sept. 24, 1858; 10x8; Gould, Augustus A. (Augustus Addison), 1805-1866
    Boston, A.L.S. 3p.and add. Friendly letter. Refers to voyage home (Boston).
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 25, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Allis, J D
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, Sept. 27, 1858; 8x5; Prince, Temple
    Versailles, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning shells.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 4, 1858; 6x4; Walcott, William H L
    Clifton, A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 7, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Cuming, Hugh, 1791-1865
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds and shells. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton]:, Oct. 9, 1858; 8-1/2x5; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 4p. Letter continued on Oct. 16. Concerning reptiles and birds. Refers to British Museum and Sclater.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 11, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Allis, J D
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds. Refers to Owen.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 19, 1858; 8x5; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Nov. 4, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Nov. 18, 1858; 8x5; Gould, John, 1804-1881
    London, A.L.S. 8p. Friendly letter. Concerning birds. Refers to Bennett and Jardine.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Dec. 20, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning a part of a skeleton.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Dec. 21, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 8p. Concerning birds and skeletons. Refers to Sclater.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Dec. 24, 1858; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Hooker, William Jackson, Sir, 1785-1865
    Kew, A.L.in 3rd.p. 2p. Collection of money.
  - Letter to Philip [sic] Eyton, Shropshire, Dec. 24, 1858; 10x8; Thomson, J R
    A.L.S. 4p.,add. Concerning the turkey buzzard of South Africa.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 17, 1858 (?); 8x5; Smuting (?), John S
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning oysters.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Jan. 9, 1859; 8-1/2x5; Blyth, Ed[ward], 1810-1873.
    Calcutta, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning natural history and birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas Campbell Eyton], Jan. 20, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Taylor, Thomas Lambe
    Stanton, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning butterflies, birds, and shells. Refers to Fraser.
  - Letter to Cha[rle]s [sic] Eyton, Shropshire, Feb. 10, 1859; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Verreaux, Édouard (Jean Baptiste Édouard), 1810-1868
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In French. Offers to sell him birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Feb. 17, 1859; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Charlesworth, Edward
    Oxford, A.L.S. 4p. Friendly letter. Concerning fossils.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], March 22, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 1p. Concerning reptiles. Refers to several books.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Shropshire, April 18, 1859; 10-1/2x8; Fraser, Louis, fl. 1866
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. Earthquake. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, May 6, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Murray, W O
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Has forwarded skins and skeleton.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, May 19, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Murray, W O
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 30, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 3p. Business.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], June 3, 1859; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Murray, Andrew, 1812-1878
    Edinburgh, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning entomology and birds. Refers to Jardine.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Shropshire, June 24, 1859; 8-1/2x6; Nylander, William, 1822-1899
    Helsingfors, A.L.S. 1p.and add. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 14, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Hyndman, George C
    Belfast, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning oysters.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 15, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. Concerning birds. Refers to Cuvier.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], July 17, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Henslow, J. S. (John Stevens), 1796-1861
    Suffolk, A.L.S. 4p. Friendly letter. Concerning plants. Refers to Harvey.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 5, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to Thomas C. Eyton, Sep 25, 1859; Allis, J D
  - Letter to J. V. Stewart, Oct. 28, 1859; 8x5; Bree, Charles Robert, 1811-1886
    Portsea, A.L.S. 2p. Publication on birds of Europe.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug.13, 1860; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 9, 1860; 7x4; Houghton, William
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 10, 1860; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 11, 1860; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    Bala, A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 12, 1860; 7x4-1/2; Bree, Charles Robert, 1811-1886
    Colchester, A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 17, 1860; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    Chester, A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Jan. 5, 1861; 7x4-1/2; Bree, Charles Robert, 1811-1886
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], March 27, 1862; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
    A.L. 4p. Incomplete. Concerning fish. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 14, 1862; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter. Refers to Günther.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Oct. 24, 1863; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Nov. 15, 1863; 7x4-1/2; Blyth, Ed[ward], 1810-1873.
    Liverpool, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter. Refers to Gurney.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Nov. 21, 1863; 7x4-1/2; Gurney, John Hampden, 1802-1862
    Bournemouth, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds. Refers to Blyth.
  - Letter to E[dward] Blyth, Dec. 9, 1863; 7x4-1/2; Asiatic Society of Bengal
    Calcutta, L.S.: Edw[ar]d B. Cowell. 3p. Congratulations on pension.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Feb. 12, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Eyton, Robert William, 1815-1881
    Kent, A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 11, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Blyth, Ed[ward], 1810-1873.
    Dublin, A.L.S. 4p. Has been robbed. Asks for loan.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 14, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Blyth, Ed[ward], 1810-1873.
    Dublin, A.L.S. 4p. Friendly letter. Thanks for the money. Business. Refers to the Asiatic Society of Bengal.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 19, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning fishes and birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 16, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Blyth, Ed[ward], 1810-1873.
    Dublin, A.L.S. 4p. Enc. Friendly letter. Is working for the Asiatic society of Bengal. Encloses sketches of antlers.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 12, 1864; 8x5; Verreaux, Édouard (Jean Baptiste Édouard), 1810-1868
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. In French. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 4, 1864; 8x5; Verreaux, Édouard (Jean Baptiste Édouard), 1810-1868
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. In French. Business.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Oct.5, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 30, 1864; 8x5; Verreaux, Édouard (Jean Baptiste Édouard), 1810-1868
    Paris, A.L.S. 1p. In French. Business. Refers to Fraser.
  - Letter to Thomas C. Eyton, Nov 2, 1864; Salvin, Osbert, 1835-1898
    On subscription for Ibis.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Nov. 8, 1864; 10x8; Liverpool (England). Public Libraries, Museums, and Art Gallery
    Liverpool, Printed L. filled in in ms.S.: Charles Morley. 1p. Thanks for donation of specimens.
  - Letter to [Edwin C.] Prince, Sept., 1865; 8x5; Bree, Charles Robert, 1811-1886
    A.L.S. 1p. Forwards prints for Eyton's publication.
  - Letter to [Thomas] C. Eyton, July 27, 1865; 7x4-1/2; Ray Society
    Lewisham, A.L.S.: H. T. Stainton. 3p. Concerning delinquent dues.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Sept. 15, 1865; 8x5; Prince, Edwin C
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning publications. Mentions Bree.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Oct. 19, 1865; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
    London, A.L.in 3rd.P. 3p. Asks a favor.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 3, 1865; 9x7-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 21, 1865; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Dec. 19, 1865; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 4p. Cannot purchase his collection of skeletons due to limited space.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 29, 1866; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], April 29, 1867; 7x4-1/2; Salvin, Osbert, 1835-1898
    A.L.S. 3p. Business. Concerning overdue membership dues.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 6, 1867; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter. Concerning publications.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 24, 1867; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 26, 1867; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Gray, John Edward, 1800-1875
    A.L.S. 2p. Wishes his collection of birds and skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 28, 1867; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds. Refers to Gray.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 2, 1867; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Flower, William Henry, 1831-1899
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Cannot purchase his collection of birds and skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 8, 1867; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, April 27, 1868; 7x4-1/2; Sharpe, Richard Bowdler, 1847-1909
    London, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 1, 1868; 7x4-1/2; Sharpe, Richard Bowdler, 1847-1909
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], June 20, 1868; 7x4-1/2; Huxley, Thomas Henry, 1825-1895
    London, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Oct. 28, 1868; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning fishes.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Dec. 16, 1868; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    Lancaster, A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Dec. 19, 1868; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Jan. 20, 1869; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Jan. 27, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Feb. 3, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Feb. 19, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    London, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning ducks.
  - Receipt for [Thomas C.] Eyton's book, March 6, 1869; 4-1/2x8-1/2; British Museum
    Printed D. filled in in ms.S.: T.Watts. 1p.
  - Receipt for Thomas C. Eyton's book, March 6, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Faculty of Advocates (Scotland). Library
    A.D.S.: Saml. Halkett. 1p.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 5, 1869; 8x5; Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880
    London, A.L.S. 2p. Concerning fishes.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], May 5, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning fishes.
  - Letter to R. Hobson, May 6, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Bodleian Library
    Oxford, A.L.S.: H. O. Coxe. 1p. Enc.of receipt. Received publication by Eyton. Also included is note from "Copyright Registry"
  - Letter to Tho[ma]s [C.] Eyton, May 7, 1869; 6-1/2x4; Bird, Edwin A
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 8, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Gray, George Robert, 1808-1872
    A.L.S. 1p. Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 9, 1869; 10x8; Zoological Society of London
    Printed L.filled in in ms.S.: Philip Lutley Sclater. 1p. Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 13, 1869; 8x5; Moore, T J